{
  "easyquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 1+1?",
      "answer1": "1",
      "answer2": "2",
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2+2?",
      "answer1": "3",
      "answer2": "4",
      "correct": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 3+4?",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5+3?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6+2?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 4+5?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 7+3?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "10",
      "correct": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8+4?",
      "answer1": "11",
      "answer2": "12",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9+6?",
      "answer1": "14",
      "answer2": "15",
      "correct": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10+5?",
      "answer1": "14",
      "answer2": "15",
      "correct": "15"
    }
  ]
}
